Cute Executive Officer
Starting now!
Episowde 1
Contract
Contwact.
SUPER IMPORTANT!!
A contract
is...
Contract
An absolutely
essential piece
of paper for
the company!!
A contract is an absolutely essential
piece of paper for the company!
Misplacing a contract could have
incredibly disastrous consequences!
CEO
Najimu
Mujina
(Age 5)
CEO'S
Secretary
Yuki
Karuizawa
(Age 22)
I finally finished! Lookie, Yuki!
Shazaaaaam!
SHAZAAAAAM
I cweated our company mascot chawacter!
Her name is Raccoozabeth!
Expertly done, boss.
Play Every Day
Now our company is even more adowable!
B-Boss!
Plain Old
Employee
Mayu Warito
(Age 26)
We've got trouble!
I can't find that ultra important contract anywhere!
Do you know where it might be?!
CEO
CONTRACT
Boss?!
You're holding it right now, aren't you?
GRAB
And you doodled all over it?!
I'll clean it up, so just hand it over!
But Raccoozabeth... it's my bestest drawing...
Oh, come on! Don't be ridiculous!
Ms. Yuki, talk some sense into her!
It is indeed a most superb piece of art.
A fat lot of help you are! Jeez!
streeeetch
I need Raccoozabeth!
Enough! Please just let go!
TEAR
Raccoozabeth!
Riiiip
No! The contract!
See? It's a lot
bwighter now!
Cute Executive Officer
Starting now!
Episowde 2
Complaint
Compwaint.
Plain Old
Employee
Mayu Warito
(Age 26)
Yes... my sincerest apologies...
Talking to you is a waste of time!
Put me on with your manager!
Yes... right away.
Yes, hewwo? This is Najimu!
CEO
Najimu
Mujina
(Age 5)
CEO
Huh? A k-kid?!
I'm five years owd!
How is a kid like you the manager?
It's one of the reguwations at our company.
What kind of company is this?!
I wanna give the person in charge a piece
of my mind! Just pass the phone to an adult!
Okaaay!
Your call has been transferred.
CEO'S
Secretary
Yuki Karuizawa
(Age 22)
You are now speaking to the CEO's secretary, Karuizawa.
Secretary?! I don't want no secretary, I want the CEO!
Yessir.
Hewwo there!
Why do I keep getting transferred to you?!
I'm the CEO!
Are you for real?!
So, is there a pwoblem?
Straight to the point, huh?!
Listen, I bought something from your company
and it busted before I could even use it!
I demand some compensation, hear me!
Kompensayshion? What's that?
You don't know?! Well, I suppose
that's natural for a kid your age!
It's about respect! And feelings! I won't feel okay
until you send a replacement or something!
You need things to have feelings...?
Ugh, you're killing me here.
Look, the customer is king, isn't that right?!
"King"...? But awen't you just a normal person like
me?
E-er, um... well, you should be treating me
with esteem and stuff since I paid you money...
"A-steam"...?
Oh god, it's really mortifying
to have to explain this in detail!
Uh, so...
GAH!
Whatever, just apologize to me!
All right then.
On three, let's both say "I'm sowwy". Okay?
Why me?!
Fighting is a no-no, so we both have to apowogize.
I'm sowwy for making you angry.
And you're sowwy for yelling at me.
But that's not...
Here we go! One, two...!
I'm sowwy!
I'm s-sorry...
Great! Now we're fwiends again!
My bad, I didn't mean to get so angry...
No, that's okay! Call us again sometime!
Bye bye!
That was god-like!
Machine to
Make You
Drink Coffee
Mark 1!!
GACHUUUNK
Splaaaaash
Cute Executive Officer
Starting now!
Episowde 3
Overtime
Ovwertime.
Meeting the deadline for this project is gonna be tough...
Plain Old
Employee
Mayu Warito
(Age 26)
Gotta keep
it up~
Guess I'm pulling an all-nighter today.
Good work, evewyone!
WHAM!
Wham!
Picture book!!
Toothbrush!!
Wham!
CEO
Najimu
Mujina
(Age 5)
EXCITE
Picture Book
I'm going to spend the night here, too!
I hope you realize that we're staying to work, not
have a sleepover!
7 P.M.
Tappity tap, tappity tap, tappity tap.
Picture
book
Yuki, read me a bedtime stowy.
Long, long ago, there was a young
high school girl who lived in a certain...
I can't concentrate like this.
9 p.m.
Ringtailored
(Yummy!)
Corn
Soba
Energy
Drink
Tappity tap, tappity tap, tappity tap.
Hey, Mayu!
What can I do for you?
Excite
I wanna know, do you have a cwush on any boys?
I told you, this isn't a sleepover!
11 p.m.
Super
Energy Drink
Tappity tap, tappity tap, tappity tap.
Yello
Bull
If I keep this pace up,
I think I can finish before the deadline.
Okeh... juth a rittle mowr...
Tappity tap, tappity tap, tappity tap
Tappity tap, tappity tap, tappity tap.
It's too bwight, I can't sleep.
And all that tappy noise is too loud.
Drowsy...
What did you even stay for?! Seriously!
Yuki, tuwn off the lights.
Huh?
Right away.
KERSLAM!
Nooooo!
Good night, boss.
Damn secretary! I swear I'll get you back for this!
(CEO's sleepy time)
Mandatory Lights Out Period
We are now in the mandatory lights out period.
Please retire to your bed, Ms. Mayu.
Cushy,
cushy...
Goddammit!
Goddammiiiiit!
Although I lost a chunk of data in the blackout,
I felt refreshed after some sleep and
made quick progress in the morning,
somehow finishing it all before the deadline.
Corporate Drone
Corporate Dwone.
BUZZ
BUZZ     BUZZ
Boss... what is that?
A machine of destwuction...
that targets corporate dwones!
Raccoozabeth
Mk. 2
A.KA.
Corpobliterator
(Prototype)
BUZZ    BUZZ    BUZZ    BUZZ
WHAZAAAAM
It's a prototype of the Racoozabeth Mark 2,
otherwise known as the Corpobliterator!
That's a mouthful!
Employee
Expatriate
Garcia
(Age 22)
No need for
severance pay
if you sever
their heads first
BUZZ    BUZZ
What's it for? A new way to lay people off?
Gosh no!
BUZZ    BUZZ
It's the opposite!
This machine was made to destwoy anything that
might cause people to become corporate dwones!
BEEP
BOOP
It has a super A.I. that can identify stuff like workplace
hawassment or useless busy work in an instant!
Extortion
Free Overtime
Pointless
Meetings
Then kablamo!
Talk about serious overkill!
BUZZ
BUZZ    BUZZ
Why create something so dangerous?!
It's impossible to destwoy the rotten system
in our society without going to extremes like this!
I don't want to see anymore suffering!
No more of the youth should have
their futures taken fwom them.
Boss...
That's the deal!
We're deploying these babies acwoss the country,
so build 100 of them!
And get it done by tomorrow!
BUZZ
Was forced
to construct
the prototype
in one night
BUZZ
There's your target!
BEEP
BOOP
She was obliterated.
GRWAAAAARR...
Cute Executive Officer
Starting now!
Episowde 4
Bankruptcy
Bankwuptcy.
Looking back, nothing in my life ever turned out well.
My business venture failed,
the company went bankrupt...
And the new products I came up with to try and
keep it all from falling apart was a gigantic dud.
Milk &
Raddish
Soup
STOCK OF
100,000
CASES
I was left with 100,000 unsold cases.
I just had no brains for business whatsoever.
Forgive me, my wife.
And my employees...
Take off!
Take off! Take off!
Why is there a little girl on the top of this building?
Go! Fly away!
What do you think you're doing?
Huh? I'm flying paper airpwanes!
Go on! Take off! Take off! Take off!
Take Off!
I'd really appreciate if you'd stop shouting that...
But I can't get them to go very far for some reason!
It's probably because you're not folding them right.
You have to firmly press down all the folds one-by-one.
Then when you let them go,
you have to let your wrist snap. Like this.
Whoa! Amazing!
You're super good at sending things flying, mister!
No doubt about that. I sent my company
flying right into the sun the other day.
That's so cool. I can't make anything fly good yet.
Great job, mister!
I did something great, eh?
I guess I'll pick myself up and
give it another shot, the sky's the limit!
Thanks for your help, missy!
Consider that juice a gift!
He left.
Boss, I've been looking for you.
Wow, this is super yummy! Who makes this stuff?!
I'll look it up for you right away.
I'm happy to
be here today!!
KABLAAAM
Cute Executive Officer
Starting now!
Episowde 5
Office Cleaning
Office Cweaning.
Expatriate Garcia, Mujina Company Employee.
Mujina Company
Employee
Expatriate
Garcia
(Age 22)
Her nationality and employment history are unknown.
Nationality:
Unknown
Employment
History: Unknown
Her main jobs at the office are making tea and cleaning.
Duties include:
Tea service
and cleaning
I can't read or write in Japanese,
so office work is beyond me!
How did you even get hired...?
Mujina Company
Earnings Data
But ever since you started here, the company earnings
have skyrocketed for some reason.
What's up with that?
That's easy.
CLEANING
It's all thanks to the cleaning that I do!
Morning
Take Out
Garbage
Clean
Windows
In the morning...
Afternoon
Bathroom
Cleaning
In the afternoon...
Mopping
So, I hear you're working on a plan to crush
those arrogant clods at the Mujina Company?
Yes! And I would love to have
a fine congressman like yourself onboard.
Well, we have a long history of scratching
each other's backs. How can I say no?
Oh sir! Thank you!
Running a puny company like that out of business is as
easy as shooting fish in a barrel!
Everyone's job goes a lot smoother,
because I'm always out there cleaning house!
Thanks for everything you do, Garcy!
Hometown
Hometown.
Dango
I'm back from my trip home and
I brought everyone a treat.
Thank you!
What kind of pwace is your hometown, Mayu?
My family runs a typical rice farm out
in the boring old countryside.
I got saddled with a ton of veggies on my way back.
Yeah, that sounds like the countryside.
What is your hometown like, boss?
Mine's pretty typical too!
France
Tycoons
A typical house out in the boring
old countryside of France!
There's nothing typical about that!
I always get saddled with lots
of real estate on my way back.
That's completely unrelatable to us common folk!
What about your hometown, Garcy?
Well...
Please let me fight by your side, mother!
Absolutely not, Garcia! You must flee!
But why?! I'm already 10 years old, I know how to fight!
We will hold them off here.
Garcia, you are the future of our tribe.
You must survive this day and
then see to it that our tribe rises again!
Now, hurry! Flee before the enemy discovers you!
If my fate is to be one with the stars,
then I shall watch over you from heaven.
My beloved daughter...
Amma! Amma!
Amma...!
Garcy?
It's just another typical place!
Oh really?
Cute Executive Officer
Starting now!
Episowde 6
My First Errand
My First Ewwand.
Circus Bakery
Welcome!
U-umm, ahh...
Do you have bwead loafs for sale?
HEH
Aw, she must be on her very first errand.
Yes, we sure do!
How many would you like?
Pwease give me 200 of them!
Wait...
a retailer?
Wait... a retailer?
A-are you sure? You don't mean 2?
No, 200!
Wh-what are you going to do with so many?
You're not running a business, right?
We're gonna start up a sandwich shop!
Whoa, she really is in the retail biz.
Do you do periodic reorders here?
Periodic
Reorders
Errand runners don't use that kind of lingo!
I would like to get a sales quote!
Sales
Quote
Seriously, she's got the vocabulary of a real
professional!
Uhhh... that's a lot of bread, am I correct in
assuming you want it delivered monthly... little miss?
Yeah!
Monthly...?
Wait, is that what they said? Monthly? Or was it weekly?
I think... that we want 200 loaves a day... pwease...
This is where the childlike confusion kicks in?!
The difference between monthly and daily is huge,
so if you're wrong it could be a major problem!
Ordering 200 loaves daily would mean you'd be making
over 6000 sandwiches in a single day, you know?!
Th-that's just fine... probably.
No, it's most certainly not fine!
You have to try to remember!
I'm back!
Fist pump!
Fist
Pump
I finished running my ewwand!
Chuckle
The boss is growing up more and more every day!
And thus began
the hell of 200
loaves of bread
being delivered
to us day after day.
And thus began the hell of 200 loaves of bread
being delivered to us day after day.
Sandwiches
Get 'Em
Cheap!
Cute Executive Officer
Starting now!
Episowde 7
Interview
Intewview.
Why does the train have to be late
on the day of my interview of all days?!
I've only got 10 minutes until it starts!
Mommy! Where are you?
Lost Child
Carrying all this is so hard on my back.
If only someone could help me...
Elderly Woman
I'd really love to help,
but my future is at stake here! Sorry!
Wild Alligator
Ba-bum!
Christ! Talk about being in mortal danger!
Alligator...
Why is there a wild alligator in
our law-abiding country of Japan?!
Whatever, I have to save that girl!
But I have no time!
Alligator...
Alligator!
BASH
Ya damn gator! Let that poor girl go!
Take this! And this! And this! And this!
BASH
Alligator!
Smash
Alligator! Alligator!
CRASH
BONK
Alligator...
What was a wild alligator doing here?
A foreign lady gave it to me and said
"they're delicious if you grill them up".
The hell she do that for?
I'm sowwy to bother you, lady.
Don't you have a job to get to?
Nah. Besides, I can't go looking like this.
And more importantly...
My job is totally meaningless compared
to the painful look that I saw on your face.
You're a failure of an employee, huh?
Some thanks I get for saving you!
Hey Mayu, I've been meaning to ask you something.
What was the reason behind
your transfer to this company?
A wild alligator.
Huh? What's that?
While I'm at it, let me
walk you home.
Well, instead
of home, I need
to go back to
my company...
Company?
Cute Executive Officer
Starting now!
Episowde 8
Cholesterol
Cholestewol.
Fatty Ramen
Aw man, I just wanna eat all the ramen and BBQ...
Groooowl
But the doctor told me I wasn't supposed to.
Sushi Heaven
Pork Cutlets
Black Beef Steak
Dammit... there's just too much temptation in the city.
I'll go to the park.
Siizzzzle
Why are they BBQing in the park?!
Woo
Why are
they BBQing
in the park...?
Japanese
Black Cattle
Yay!
Stop, stop!
A5 grade beef
is wasted
on children
like you!
SIIIIIIZZLE
Stop, stop! A5 grade beef is wasted on children like you!
God, it looks so delicious.
GULP
Would you like to have some meat with us, mister?
Really? Well, I guess if you're offering...
DUUUUMP
Coarse Salt
Here ya go!
Isn't that way
too much salt?
Isn't that way too much salt? Are you trying to kill me?!
...Are you trying
to kill me?
And also!
Cheese!
Milt! Goosefish liver!
A fat load of salmon roe!
More Likely To Cause
Death Than Gout
GLOOOOOOOOM
The fully-loaded steak of decadence is complete!
More like a guaranteed heart attack on a plate!
gloooom
Go on, dig in!
Uh no, that's way too unhealthy for me.
Don't you know, mister?
Huh?
Greasy and salty foods are all super yummy!
There's no way they could be unhealthy!
gloooom
No, they are some of the worst things you could possibly
eat. Why did you make them sound so innocent...?
From that moment
on, the man swore
to adhere to his
doctor's advice as
closely as possible.
From that moment on, the man swore to adhere
to his doctor's advice as closely as possible.
Annual Physical
Annual Physwical.
Medical Checkup Results
Grade:  D
Re-examination Needed
Ugh... a re-examination, huh?
Why do you look so sad, mister?
Oh, you're that girl from the other day.
My checkup said that I'm as sick as a dog...
Sick as a dog, huh?
Okay, then I'll help make you feel all bwetter!
Really? Thank you!
Well, let's get going!
Wait, little girl…"sick as a dog" is just
an expression, I'm not actually a dog.
Huh?
Why are you talking? Dogs should only say woof.
She's disciplining me?!
Discipline
Our first step is taking you on a nice, long walk!
Come with me, Poochie!
N-no, listen, I...
Fetch!
Not until I say okay!
Poochie
Good boy, good boy!
Hospital
Outstanding!
Sparkle sparkle!
You've improved so much since
I last saw you that I hardly recognized you!
A much healthier diet and a huge boost in exercise, I see.
Did you start going to the gym or take up a sport?
Woof!
Woof
Excuse me?!
The man finally obtained an A grade on his checkup,
but it came at the cost of his humanity.
The man finally
obtained an A grade
on his checkup,
but it came at the
cost of his humanity.
Cute Executive Officer
Starting now!
Episowde 9
TV Shoot
CEO of the Mujina Company: Najimu Mujina.
Mujina Company CEO
Najimu Mujina
Circus Bakery
Hoping to discover the secrets behind the rapid growth
of her company, we tailed her on a typical day of work.
Expert
The Methods of a CEO
The CEO gets an early start in the mornings.
Expert
The Methods of a CEO
She goes to the park at 6 AM
before heading to the office.
She gets exercise every morning by playing around.
It's a unique approach.
Woosh...
PANT
5 hours have passed since she began to play.
It's 11 AM and she has yet to visit the office.
Smoosh, smoosh, smoosh, smoosh...
Huh? What is going on, Ms. Najimu?
What? I'm building a sand castle.
No, that's not what I mean!
Expert
The Methods of a CEO
Circus
Bakery
Afterwards, she partakes in lunch.
Then, at 1 PM, she arrives at the office.
Peace! Peace!
Stop!
Slide!
Now then.
CEO
My apowogies. I can't pay much attention
to the camera from here on out.
Great! This is what we wanted to see!
The CEO finally gets down to business
SNORE
FLOP...
A nap. For 2 whole hours.
SNORE
Then at 3 PM, she wakes up.
Excuse me, Ms. Najimu. May I ask what
your schedule is for the rest of the day?
I'm going back to the park after I have a wittle snack!
What about your job?!
Play Every Day
We came to shoot you doing work,
but all you do is goof around!
Huh? Sure, but...
All I want in my life is to do fun things!
Only wanting to do fun things
Those words gave us a glimpse
into the ideology of this CEO.
Work is often thought of by many as a painful
experience, but by learning to make it something fun
Featuring: Najimu Mujina
Narrator / Director: Deiri Kuta
Special Thanks: Mujina Company
it will naturally become a beneficial part of our lives.
Filming: Tatsuo Kamera
Production: Mhk
The first step is to focus only on the fun things.
Clench
That's the message I'm getting from watching her run
out the door to the park!
I guarantee there is no deep message
in any of what she does.
Cute Executive Officer
Starting now!
Episowde 10
Presents
Pwesents.
A master who is recognized in his craft the world over.
A genius who produces incredibly chilling
and demonic works of art.
The sculptor, Tanryusai Suda.
Sculptor:
Tanryusai
Suda
With his persnickety personality,
he is pretty much a demon himself.
He does not do business for money,
and instead only works for those he is personally fond of.
That's the deal, so please do
your best to stay on his good side.
He's apparently ultra scary if you make him angry!
No pwoblem! No pwoblem!
We brought him a nice pwesent
so I'm sure he'll agree to work for us!
Rage!
Get outta here!
YA DIPSHITS!
Did you seriously think you could just win me over
with some munchies and booze?!
P-please sir! Just hear us out!
I hate when people bring me cheap shit
like that more than anything!
And so... we would be really
honored to work with you, sir...
Please, accept this as a small token of fwiendship.
TWITCH
Fwish fwish fwish!
FWISH
Clunk!
Together We Are Trash Cure
Cure Burnables
It's a Trash Cure figure.
Huh? You don't like it?
Maybe you're a bigger fan of Cure Incombustibles
instead of Cure Burnables?
CLATTER CLATTER CLATTER
SHAKE SHAKE SHAKE
My life is over...
Tell me something, girlie. Why would you bring this?
Huh? Because it's a super good anime.
Well, girlie...
Would you mind telling me a bit more about Trash Cure?
Trashy-trash!
Actually, my granddaughter is a huge fan of this show.
What kind of gift do you think she'd like?
The transformation toys, for sure!
And make sure you don't fowget the wand!
I see! There are so many series,
I don't really know which is good.
So, is it a safe choice to go with the newest one?
The new series is nice, but the owd series is
getting a movie soon so it's gonna be super hot!
By the way, this outfit was used in
the movie from the third series!
This is such a huge help!
What?
Oh, the job? I'm in, of course!
So please teach me some more!
Oh gosh, if you insist!
Waaaah
Thank god...!
A business relationship was forged
and a Trash Cure friend was made.
A business relationship
was forged and a
Trash Cure friend was made.
Yuki, find something nice
and wrap it up for him, k?
Roger.
ZOOM
PLOP
Cute Executive Officer
Starting now!
Episowde 11
Design
Design.
You want me to redo it?
Mujina Company
Raccoozabeth Mark 3
Character Design
Well, it is super adowable.
Do you mind if I added some stuff to it?
Go ahead, feel free!
Seriously? She's gonna take my
perfectly cute design and shit all over it?
Clients like this suck.
They always wanna interject their own ideas.
But nothing good ever comes from letting a total
amateur fiddle around with design.
I did it!
Whatever. I'll just nod and smile
and get this job over with.
Okay! Let me take a look.
Raccoon
Feels So Good
An eldritch abomination?!
I would be happy if you could proceed
with this as the main inspiration.
What kind of inspiration...?
What kind of
inspiration...?
There's no way something this freaky would sell! And
unleashing it upon the world would only dirty my name!
Um, well...
Oh, wait a second!
It would look cooler with wings on it!
And I want it to poop ice cream!
Oh, and also, um, it's body should shine really pwetty
like glitter...
I had forgotten...
Back when I first started drawing,
I felt totally unstoppable. Like I could create anything.
It made me happy and I had so much fun.
Time just flew by.
Ms. Najimu, may I make one suggestion?
If this little cutie had a friend,
what do you think it would look like?
What?! A friend?!
I know, I know! It would be a wabbit
that uses its ears to make crepes!
That's wonderful! Then how do you feel
about making it vomit whipped cream?
Oh! That's a great idea!
How about it shoots something out of its hands?
It's just gotta be strawberries!
What this conversation really needs is a naysayer!
Raccoozabeth
Mark 3, now
redesigned into
a complete
eldritch abomination.
Raccoozabeth Mark 3, now redesigned
into a complete eldritch abomination.
Ms. Yuki! We need you!
You're the only one who knows how
to stop the boss when she's on a rampage!
If we don't do something, our company mascot
will become a man-eating monster!
Uh, what are you looking at?
It's nothing.
Where is the boss?
To Najimu
From Mommy
This way!
Cute Executive Officer
Starting now!
Episowde 12
Pawt 1
Kidnapping
Part 1
Kidnapping Pawt 1.
T-the boss has been kidnapped?!
I only took my eyes off of her for a second...
Are you serious?
Employee
Riya Motohashi
(Age 22)
(Ex-Gangster)
Our CEO is a little girl, after all.
She's a prime target for that kinda thing.
That's true.
She must be scared stiff right now...
They'll pay! Let's get out there
and rescue the boss ourselves!
N-no way, we can't track down
the criminals who did this alone...
Let us handle this!
You guys are...!
TA DAAAAAH
I figured we might need backup, so I gave them a call!
We're all indebted to Najimu for what she did!
We'll help you out!
Rescue Operation
BLAH
I can find her in a flash using my company's network!
I'll round up some equipment that we can use!
BLAH
Here doggy! Follow this scent!
Woof!
BLAH
Okay! I've more or less figured out where she is!
Get ready to raid 'em!
That was fast!
Hold on, how are all of us going to get there at once?
BABAM!
I also came to make a delivery!
My collaborative work with Najimu! The Raccoozabeth
Mark 3 loaded with a ton of secret features!
Oh, you mean that mascot character...
RUMBLE
C'mon! Hop on!
How the hell is it this freakin' big?!
Let's move!
And how the hell does it freakin' fly?!
VROOOOOM
Move! Move!
Woof!
Boss!
Back the hell off!
KABLAAAAAAAAM
kablaaaaaaaam
Don't touch our boss!
This is total overkill!
They obviously deserved it for what they did!
Alligator.
SIZZLE
CRUNCH
CHOMP
Finish them off!
STOMP
Stomp
Um...
YAY!
Our boss is incredibly precious to us and
we'll never let you have her! You damn pervert!
We did it!
No... wait...
SIZZLE
That's my mommy.
Alligator...
Thank you for always watching after my daughter.
Cute Executive Officer
Starting now!
Episowde 12
Pawt 2
Kidnapping
Part 2
Kidnapping Pawt 2.
Hello, wonderful to meet you all.
I'm Najimu's mother.
CLATTER
Guess we jumped to the wrong conclusion!
Oh no, we did far worse than that...
Before you rushed in to save Najimu,
DOOM
did you not ponder the situation for even a second?
All of you are fully grown adults.
JOLT
Honestly...
Honestly, you all must treasure Najimu so very much.
Let's live together overseas.
You don't want to be with mommy?
Or are you worried about leaving something behind?
Our boss is incredibly precious to us...!
Everyone...
Please continue to watch after and care for my daughter.
O-of course!
Are you really sure about this?
Staying separated from your mom?
Don't be silly.
I'm the Cute Executive Officer
of Mujina Company, you know!
Let's go back to the office!
Okay!
Actually, wow! It's so great to see you guys again!
Woof!
Say, why don't we all go out for a drink after this?
Great idea!
I like the sound of that!
All right, Yuki! Make a reservwation!
Right away.
Cute Executive Officer
Starting now!
Episowde 13
Slogan
Swogan.
Okay, today's agenda...
Mujina
Company
CEO
Najimu
Mujina
(Age 5)
We're all going to decide on a company swogan!
Plain Old
Employee
Mayu Warito
(Age 26)
What do you think of this one, boss?
Always strive to reach the summit.
If I had to describe it...
It's dull.
Can't get anymore mediocre than that.
Then what did you guys come up with?!
If you go play elsewhere,
clean up your toys first.
Shazaaaaam!
SHAZAAAAAM!
Seriously?! That's the kind of thing you see in homes!
Come up with something that works for a company!
CEO'S
Secretary
Yuki
Karuizawa
(Age 22)
Ms. Yuki! Your job as secretary is to keep
the CEO on task and make her take this seriously!
BOOOOOOOM
Can clean up after herself.
The CEO gets a gold star.
How is that a company slogan?!
Quit fawning over the CEO!
You guys really need to get serious about this!
Totally!
Plain Old
Employee
Nationality
Unknown
Expatriate
Garcia
(Age 22)
There's no point if we can't actually use it!
SHRIEEEEEK!
Bleed fresh fish with
a slice to the neck
That's a freakin' survival skill!
How the hell is that supposed
to represent our company?!
Mine is literally the only one that's half-decent!
It's pretty tough to decide which is the best.
Okay! If we can't pick one,
then let's mix them all up together!
Huh?
PAT
This company only succeeds
because we all work together.
PAT
The Mujina Company is the result
of our combined efforts!
Boss...
Always strive to
play else
the CEO gets a
slice to the neck
Mujina Company
BAM
Get over here! Lemme see your neck!
Waaaah!
Do Your Jobs!
Do your jobs!
Cute Executive Officer
Starting now!
Morning Meeting
(Ending)
Mowning Meeting.
Always make
proper greetings!
The morning meeting. All employees are put in a rotation
and must give a 1 minute speech on their turn.
Uh, hello everyone, my name is Warito
and I'm the speaker for today's meeting.
I saw an interesting saying in a book
that I was reading the other day.
It said, "employees are akin to a school of sardines."
I took that to mean that we humans cannot survive
without cooperating for the greater good...
SNOOOOOORE
Hey! Wake up, you jerks!
I always come off as dreadfully boring.
How can I present my speech in a way
that people will actually listen?
I fink you need shum more razzle and dazzle.
Maybe you should play some music or something.
Dum dum dum dum dum dah dun! Wub!
Dum dum dum dum
dum dah dun!
Wub!
Greetings
y'all!
What am I, a comedy act?
Wub!
Whatever, I'll never be able to give a fun speech...
SLAAAM!
The most important pawt of a speech is
letting evewybody know how you feel!
You don't need any quotes or sayings from books!
All you have to do is speak
the words straight from your heart!
Just leave all the music and other stuff to us!
Th-thank you so much!
Some
Days Later
Some days later...
Murmur...
The morning meeting will now begin.
Uwaah. Today's speaker is...
CORPORATALLICA
Me, the wicked Corporatallica.
Sit back and listen to my hit song, "Back to the Office".
This is lit!!
Omigosh!
You rock!
WHOAAAAA!!
The metal screams of Mayu's soul
drove the crowd into a frenzy.
Everyone at the company was
especially productive that day.
Yo, wicked Corporatallica!
Please no!
For the next
few days, Mayu
was only referred
to by nickname.
For the next few days, Mayu was
only referred to by nickname.